Guide to the Service Bureau, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, 1915-1967; Accession 1969-A-005
  - Students
    - Parking stickers, 1951-1952 (Box 117, Folder 1171)
    - Suit Pressing Company, Incorporated against Yale Cold Storage (Box 117, Folder 1172)
  - Supplies records, 1942-1949 (Box 117, Folder 1173)
  - Surplus property, U.S. government
    - Board, 1945 (Box 117, Folder 1174)
    - 1945-1947 (Box 117, Folder 1175-1178)
    - 1145-1152 (Box 118, Folder 1179-1190)
    - 1945-1952 (Box 119, Folder 1191-1192)
    - 1948-1951 (Box 119, Folder 1193)
    - Dunham Laboratory, 1946-19[illegible]8 (Box 119, Folder 1194-1196)
    - Furniture from war assets, 1947 (Box 119, Folder 1197)
    - Machine tools: transferred to industry, 1952 (Box 119, Folder 1198)
    - Medical school, 1944-1949 (Box 119, Folder 1199)
    - Netallurgy, Department of, 1946 (Box 119, Folder 1200)
    - Physics, 1946-1951 (Box 119, Folder 1201)
    - Stock and maintenance, 1947-1951 (Box 119, Folder 1202)
  - Telephone applications and requisitions completed, 1950 (Box 120, Folder 1203-1204)
  - Telephone company, southern New England, 1936-1941 (Box 120, Folder 1205)
  - Time distribution, travel and office expenses, 1938-1942 (Box 120, Folder 1206)
  - Ray Tompkins House
    - Alterations and furnishings, 1932-1935 (Box 120, Folder 1207)
    - Architects, 1931-1933 (Box 120, Folder 1208-1211)
    - clients, 1931-1932 (Box 121, Folder 1212)
    - Contractors, general, 1931-1932 (Box 121, Folder 1213-1215)
    - Contractors, heating, 1932 (Box 121, Folder 1216)
    - Contractors, plumbing, 1931-1932 (Box 121, Folder 1217)
    - Contracts, 1931 (Box 121, Folder 1218)
    - Kitchen equipment, 1932 (Box 121, Folder 1219)
    - Miscellaneous, 1931-1932 (Box 121, Folder 1220)
    - "Y" club: miscellaneous, 1932 (Box 121, Folder 1221)
  - Sarah Wey Tompkins Memorial
    - Architects, 1931-1932 (Box 121, Folder 1222-1224)
    - Architects, 1933 (Box 122, Folder 1225)
    - Clients, 1931-1933 (Box 122, Folder 1226)
    - Contractors, general, 1931-1933 (Box 122, Folder 1227-1231)
    - Contractors, heating, 1931-1933 (Box 123, Folder 1232)
    - Contracts, 1931-1932 (Box 123, Folder 1233)
    - Equipment orders, 1932-1934 (Box 123, Folder 1234)
    - Miscellaneous, 1932-1933 (Box 123, Folder 1235-1236)
    - Notes and calculations, 1931-1933 (Box 123, Folder 1237)
    - Plumbing: credits and extras, 1931-1932 (Box 123, Folder 1238)
    - Refrigeration, 1931-1933 (Box 123, Folder 1239)
    - Ward units A & B: miscellaneous, 1931 (Box 123, Folder 1240-1241)
    - Ward units A & B & Farnam notes, 1931-1932 (Box 123, Folder 1242)
    - Ward unit B
      - Architects, 1931-1932 (Box 124, Folder 1243-1245)
      - Clients, 1931-1933 (Box 124, Folder 1246)
      - Contractors, electrical, 1931-1933 (Box 124, Folder 1247)
      - Contractors, general, 1931-1932 (Box 124, Folder 1248-1250)
      - Contractors, heating, 1931-1933 (Box 124, Folder 1251)
      - Extras, and credits, 1931-1932 (Box 125, Folder 1252)
      - Miscellaneous, 1931-1932 (Box 125, Folder 1253)
  - Training, Military: moves and alterations, 1942-1943 (Box 125, Folder 1254)
  - Transcribing equipment, 1944-1948 (Box 125, Folder 1255)
  - Trucks, 1947-1948 (Box 125, Folder 1256)
  - Trumbull College (Elm & College Street Dormitories)
    - Alterations and furnishings, 1933-1934 (Box 125, Folder 1257-1258)
    - Architects, 1929-1931 (Box 125, Folder 1259-1260)
    - Architects, 1931-1933 (Box 126, Folder 1261-1267)
    - Clients, 1929-1937 (Box 126, Folder 1268)
    - Contractors, electrical, 1929-1930 (Box 126, Folder 1269)
    - Contractors, general, 1929-1934 (Box 127, Folder 1270-1278)
    - Contractors, plumbing, 1932 (Box 128, Folder 1279)
    - Contracts, 1931-1933 (Box 128, Folder 1280)
    - Heating, miscellaneous, 1932-1933 (Box 128, Folder 1281)
    - Inspection report: Master's house, sketches, 1932-1933 (Box 128, Folder 1282)
    - Kitchen equipment, 1932-1933 (Box 128, Folder 1283)
    - Master's House, 1945-1946 (Box 128, Folder 1284)
    - Miscellaneous, 1929-1935 (Box 128, Folder 1285-1286)
    - Orders and requisitions, 1933 (Box 128, Folder 1287)
    - Refrigeration, 1932-1935 (Box 128, Folder 1288-1289)
    - Revisions, extras & credits, 1931-1932 (Box 128, Folder 1290-1291)
  - Tunnels
    - Block A pipe covering: from Power House to dining hall to new library, 1929 (Box 128, Folder 1292)
    - College and Grove Streets, 1931 (Box 128, Folder 1293)
    - Institute of Human Relations to Private Patient Pavilion, 1929 (Box 128, Folder 1294)
    - Vanderbuilt-Sheffield, 1939 (Box 128, Folder 1294a)
    - York Square, 1927 (Box 128, Folder 1294b)
  - Underground duct lines, 1930-1931 (Box 129, Folder 1295)
  - Union dues: check off list, 1944-1950 (Box 129, Folder 1296)
  - University Service Bureau: sprinklerssystem, 1927 (Box 129, Folder 1297)
  - Vanderbuilt Sheffield: alterations, 1939 (Box 129, Folder 1298-1301)
  - Vehical registration, 1950 (Box 129, Folder 1302)
  - Vernon Hall, 217 Park Street, 1949-1950 (Box 129, Folder 1303)
  - Veterans' Administration, 1944-1947 (Box 129, Folder 1304)
  - Veterans' employment regulations, 1945-1947 (Box 129, Folder 1305)
  - Wage Hour Law, State-Federal, 1933-1941 (Box 129, Folder 1306)
  - Wages: government regulations, 1950-1951 (Box 129, Folder 1307)
  - Waiver forms, undated (Box 129, Folder 1308)
  - Wall, 123 and High, 137 Streets: Services to, 1945 (Box 129, Folder 1309)
  - War Assets Administration, 1945-1948 (Box 130, Folder 1310-1312)
  - War Production Board
    - Compliance Survey, 1944-1949 (Box 130, Folder 1313)
    - Equipment authorization, 1943-1945 (Box 130, Folder 1314)
    - Priprities, 1943-1946 (Box 130, Folder 1315)
  - Welch Hall: alterations: blueprint, 1938 (Box 130, Folder 1316)
  - William Wirt Winchester Hospital
    - Closing buildings, 1940 (Box 130, Folder 1317)
    - Electrical: general, 1930-1933 (Box 130, Folder 1318)
    - Engine room, miscellaneous, 1933-1935 (Box 130, Folder 1319)
    - Laundry
      - Clients, 1932-1933 (Box 130, Folder 1320)
      - Contractors, electrical, 1932 (Box 130, Folder 1321)
      - Contractors, equipment, 1932 (Box 130, Folder 1322)
      - Contractors, general, 1932 (Box 130, Folder 1323)
        - Monorail & hoist, 1932-1933 (Box 130, Folder 1324)
        - Piping, 1932 (Box 130, Folder 1325)
      - Miscellaneous, 1927-1930 (Box 130, Folder 1326)
      - Notes and calculations, 1932 (Box 130, Folder 1327)
    - Letters, general, 1930-1933 (Box 130, Folder 1328)
    - Survey, miscellaneous, 1933 (Box 130, Folder 1329)
  - Withholding Tax, 1943-1945 (Box 131, Folder 1330)
  - Womens' Dormitory, 1932-1933 (Box 131, Folder 1331)
  - Woolsey Hall, 1929-1930 (Box 131, Folder 1332)
  - Woolsey and Memorial Hall, 1948-1950 (Box 131, Folder 1333)
  - Wright Hall, 1933 (Box 131, Folder 1334)
  - X-ray machine surplus, 1946 (Box 131, Folder 1335)
  - Yale Daily News Building: miscellaneous, 1931-1933 (Box 131, Folder 1336)
  - Yale Dining Hall: miscellaneous, sketches, 1930-1931 (Box 131, Folder 1337)
  - Yale News, 1948-1951 (Box 131, Folder 1338)
  - Yale Record Building: re: steam service, 1931 (Box 131, Folder 1339)
  - Y.M.C.A. Junior College, New Haven, 1950 (Box 131, Folder 1340)
  - Zoning Appeals: G.I. Houses, 1946-1951 (Box 131, Folder 1341-1342)